It would be great to know what will happen before it happens, wouldn't it?
如果能未卜先知 是不是很棒？
Traders sometimes try to forecast volatility in order to anticipate the market.
交易者有时候尝试通过预测波动率来预测市场趋势
The general thinking is that it's easier to predict volatility than price,
通常 预测波动率比预测价格更容易
volatility tends to be sticky.
波动率往往具有粘性
A volatile market trading day is often followed by another volatile one.
当前市场波动率高时 随后的交易日市场波动率也高
When you're trying to model volatility,
在对波动率建模时
you can use a special form of the autoregressive model called ARCH,
可以使用特殊形式的自回归模型 称为 ARCH
which stands for, autoregressive conditionally heteroscedastic.
它是自回归条件异方差性的简称
Okay, now those are some really big words,
这几个词比较深奥
so let's break it down.
我挨个介绍下
Autoregressive simply means that
自回归表示
the current value is somehow related to the recent past values.
当前值与最近的过去值有关系
Heteroscedastic means that the variable we're trying to
异方差性表示我们尝试建模的变量
model may have different magnitudes of variability at different time points.
在不同的时间点可能具有不同的变化性大小
The magnitude of variability is commonly measured using variance.
变化性大小通常用方差衡量
Finally, conditional here, refers to a constraint we place in this model,
最后 条件性是指对模型设置的约束条件
which limits the heteroscedastic property to be
该条件会将异方差性限制为
conditionally dependent on the previous value or values of the variable.
对变量的以前值有依赖性
An arch model looks really similar to the formula
ARCH 模型看起来与
we had for an exponentially weighted moving average.
之前的指数加权移动平均公式很像
The current variance is a weighted sum of past squared log returns,
当前方差等于过去平方对数收益率的加权和
but now we think of the weights as being parameters of a model.
现在我们将权重看做模型的参数
For example, in an arch one model,
例如 在 ARCH(1) 模型中
if rt represents the log return of a stock at time t,
如果 rt 表示股票在时间 t 的对数收益率
then we say that its variance is equal to alpha zero,
那么它的方差等于
plus alpha one, times r t minus one squared.
α0+α1*r(t-1)^2
Alpha zero and alpha one are the two parameters of the model.
α0 和 α1 是模型的两个参数
You can think about alpha zero as representing a baseline variance,
可以将 α0 看做基准方差
and alpha one as waiting the contribution to
将 α1 看做上个时间点的对数收益率
the model of the log return at the previous time point.
对模型的贡献权重
This can be extended to an arch m model,
然后延伸到 ARCH(m) 模型
where the variance is conditionally dependent on m past timesteps.
其中方差有条件地依赖于 m 个过去的时间步
Note that here, the variance is being modeled only based on the squared log returns.
注意 这里的方差仅是通过对数收益率的平方来建模的
We can also add terms to make
我们还可以添加其他项
the current variance dependent on previous estimates of the variance.
使当前方差依赖于方差之前的估算值
To address this, you could modify the expression to include
我们可以修改表达式
terms with previous variance values denoted as sigma squared.
并包含之前的方差值（用 σ^2 表示）
This is known as the GARCH,
称为 GARCH
or generalized arch model.
或泛化 ARCH 模型
And you can parameterize it as GARCH m, n,
并参数化为 GARCH(m,n)
where m is the number of log return terms,
m 表示对数收益率项的数量
and n is the number of variants terms to include in the model.
n 表示模型中包含的方差项数量
Once you're satisfied with a model you've built,
对构建的模型满意后
it's time to think about how you might use it to make trading decisions.
就需要思考如何使用模型做出交易决策了
You may choose to generate buy,
你可以选择直接根据预测
sell signals directly based on your predictions,
创建买卖信号
or you may use it in an indirect way.
或者间接地使用预测
You can analyze past signal returns and see if it has somehow correlated with volatility.
你可以分析过去的信号收益率 看看它是否与波动率有关
For example, it's well known that certain strategies do better with higher volatility,
例如 众所周知 某些策略在高波动率时期业绩更好
and then you can choose to activate that strategy only during high volatility periods.
你可以选择仅在高波动率时期激活这种策略